wakanda.org 2019-05-09

# Legal Notice | Wakanda FullStack JavaScript Platform

**Legal Notice**

This website (hereafter referred to as the “ **Website** ”) is published by Wakanda, a simplified joint stock company, with a capital of 100,000.00 euros, whose registered office is located at 66 route de Sartrouville - 78230 Le Pecq, France, and which is registered with the Trade and Companies Register of Nanterre under the number 804 650 190, hereinafter referred to as " **Wakanda** ". 

  * Contact: [social@wakanda.io](mailto:social@wakanda.io)
  * Phone: +33 (0)1 30 53 92 00.

## INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY

This entire Website is protected by French and international legislation on copyright, trademarks and intellectual property, both as they are applicable to its form (structure, layout, display, database, software etc.) and to its content (texts, trademarks, logos, images, sounds, videos, games etc.). 

The contents displayed on the Website, and any software necessary to the display and the processing of this website are exclusive property of Wakanda and/or its licensors. In particular, the French and international trademarks “Wakanda” and “Wakanda’s logo” are registered trademarks under number 3669677 / 1 217 789 as to the international trademarks, and numbers 1039191 / 402 2850 as to the French trademarks.

Any reproduction, representation, diffusion or re-diffusion, in whole or in part, of any content of the Website on any medium or by any means whatsoever, as well as any sale, resale, retransmission or any other act tending to make such contents available to any third party in any manner whatsoever shall be strictly prohibited. Any fraudulent accessing, or remaining, fraudulent introduction of data, fraudulent deletion or modification of data, of, and into the automated data processing system which constitutes the Website, as well as any obstructing, or interfering with the functioning of the Website are strictly forbidden. Any reverse engineering of, or attempt to reverse engineering, the software which operates the Website is strictly forbidden, except as otherwise specified in third parties’ software license agreement, if any. 

## PRIVACY

Wakanda does not require users to disclose their personal data. However, to provide you a full and suitable access to the Website’s services, you may have to register by entering certain personal data such as your email for instance. 

Wakanda hereby informs you that all such personal data as you may provide online are intended for internal use by Wakanda and can also be shared with legal entities of 4D group, as well as to its subcontractors, to the extent necessary for data processing. Said data shall not be disclosed to third parties other than third parties that host or are involved in the contents or operation of the Website, except with your prior authorization. Your personal data collected by Wakanda are solely dedicated (i) to operate and improve the Website, services and offerings available through the Website and (ii) to communicate with you and respond to your inquiries.

In no event shall your personal data be shared or transferred to any third parties except to the aforementioned third parties.

Wakanda undertakes to take all such reasonable measures that may be available to it in order to keep said personal data confidential. 

Wakanda reminds you that, pursuant to the French law Informatique et Libertés January, 6th 1978 on information technologies, data processing and individual freedoms, as amended, you are entitled to access your personal information and to have it amended, updated or deleted, where such information is incorrect, incomplete or outdated. You may also, on legitimate grounds, object to the processing of your personal information. Such objection may, however, disallow Wakanda from providing some services.    
This Data intended to be in touch with you and send you the intended communication: the information you provide will be transferred to MailChimp for processing as we use it as our marketing automation platform. 

In accordance with Regulation ( EU) 2016/679 on the protection of personal data, you have the following rights over your data: rights of access, right of rectification, right of deletion, right to forget, right to limit processing, right to portability. You can also set guidelines for the retention, erasure, and disclosure of your personal data after your death. you have the right to access, modify and rectify information concerning you. 

You also have a right to object to the processing of your personal data for legitimate reasons, as well as a right to object to this data being used for commercial prospecting purposes. 

To exercise your rights, at any time by:

  * sending an e-mail to [social@wakanda.io](mailto:social@wakanda.io)
  * sending a letter to the Data Protection Officer of 4D, accompanied by a photocopy of an identity document bearing your signature, to the following postal address: 4D, 66 Route de Sartrouville. Parc les Erables - Bâtiment 4 - 78230 or Le Pecq - France

Besides, personal data, which may enable indirect identification, may also be collected and processed in order to better manage your connection and browsing on the website. Therefore, the Website may use "cookies". A cookie is a text file stored by your browser in order to authenticate you while browsing on the Website. You can prevent your browser from storing "persistent cookies" by configuring your browser in such way. You can see more details about the use of cookies by the Website at: <http://www.wakanda.io/our-cookies-policy>
